In order to run the simulator
ローカルマシン上でシミュレーターを
in autonomous mode on my local machine,
自律モードで実行するために
I'm going to first clone the GitHub repo for the project.
まずプロジェクトのGitHubリポジトリを複製します
This repo provides the drive.py file
このレポジトリはdrive.pyファイルを提供します
that will load my saved model and use it
このファイルは 保存されたモデルをロードし
to make steering predictions.
それを使ってステアリングの予測を立てます
Now, I'll copy the saved model from the AWS instance
保存されたモデルをAWSインスタンスからローカルマシンにコピーし
to my local machine, then I'll run drive.py and pass my model
drive.pyを実行して
file as an argument.
モデルファイルを引数として渡します
drive.py is running now, waiting for the simulator
drive.pyは現在実行中で
to start in autonomous mode.
シミュレーターが自律モードで起動するのを待っています
When I launch the simulator this time,
今回はシミュレーターを起動したら
I'll select autonomous mode.
自律モードを選択します
I can see from the output in the terminal that drive.py
ターミナルの出力から drive.pyがモデルに基づいて
is successfully predicting steering measurements based
ステアリング角の測定値を正しく予測していることがわかります
on my model, which is great.
これはよいことです
I can also see that my car is driving terribly,
さらに車の運転状況が酷いこともわかります
which is not so great.
これはよくないことです
It's not going very fast, because it's
左右にぶれながら進んでいるため
spending so much time swerving from side to side.
スピードは上がりません
This is actually a pretty good start.
実際にはかなり良いスタートです
The network doesn't drive well, but I didn't really
ネットワークの運転はうまくありませんが
expect it to.
それを期待していたわけでもありません
What I really wanted was to verify
ここでやりたかったのは モデルをトレーニングし
that I could train a model, save that model,
モデルを保存しそのモデルを使って
and then use that model to drive the vehicle in the simulator.
シミュレーターで車両を運転できることを検証することでした
All of that works, so now I just have to improve the model.
すべてうまくいったので これからモデルを改良していきます